Now this is an exercise that I call stitching stitching means again to bring things together like you're
现在这是一个我称之为缝合的练习，缝合意味着再次像你一样把东西放在一起
sewing like you're sewing clothes.
像缝衣服一样缝。
So when we stitch things together we're trying to combine them.
因此，当我们将事物缝合在一起时，我们会尝试将它们结合起来。
We're trying to merge them together.
我们正在尝试将它们合并在一起。
The reason we do this exercise is to understand ideas and then link them together in a way that is coherent.
我们做这个练习的原因是理解想法，然后以一种连贯的方式将它们联系在一起。
That means it all makes sense.
这意味着一切都说得通。
Now this might seem a little bit like the sort of fill in the blank exercises or exams that you did
现在这看起来有点像你做的那种填空练习或考试
in middle school or high school and I guess it kind of is except you don't know where the blanks are.
在中学或高中，我想这有点像除了你不知道空白在哪里。
And so it's kind of a more advanced version of fill in the blanks.
所以这是一种更高级的填空方法。
We've got a continuous story here.
我们在这里有一个连续的故事。
The rules are that you can't really change the order.
规则是你不能真正改变顺序。
You can only insert or put in other words.
您只能插入或换句话说。
That's the only thing you can do.
这是你唯一能做的。
So what you can do to practice this on your own is basically maybe look at an article or a book and
所以你可以自己做的练习基本上是看一篇文章或一本书，然后
pick out some of the key words write them down in order like I've done here.
挑出一些关键词按照我在这里所做的顺序写下来。
This is one that I've I've written myself and then write down or speak if you want to speak that's OK.
这是我自己写的，然后写下来或者说，如果你想说话没关系。
The whole thing.
整个东西。
Don't look at the original do it in your own way fit it together in a way that makes sense to you but
不要看原版 以你自己的方式去做
force yourself to keep everything in order and you can make as many sentences as you want.
强迫自己保持一切井井有条，你可以随心所欲地造句。
So now we're going back to the idea of syntax.
所以现在我们回到语法的概念。
We can put things together in creative ways depending on what makes the most sense or maybe what's the
我们可以以创造性的方式将事物组合在一起，这取决于什么是最有意义的，或者可能是什么
most interesting.
最有趣的。
So let's actually try this one.
所以让我们实际试试这个。
Let's do this together again.
让我们再次一起做这件事。
We're going to be basically just building sentences and putting them together as we like.
我们将基本上只是构建句子并将它们按照我们喜欢的方式组合在一起。
So I've written them like this just because it's I think easier to see each separate word I've capitalized.
所以我把它们写成这样只是因为我认为更容易看到我大写的每个单独的单词。
Each word doesn't have to be capitalized.
每个单词不必大写。
I put a period I put a period after each each word.
我在每个单词后面加上句号。
Again that doesn't have to be there it's just a way to to organize this.
同样，它不必在那里，它只是一种组织它的方式。
So let's let's start.
让我们开始吧。
How do we begin this.
我们如何开始这个。
So we're starting with the time we're starting with a month.
所以我们从一个月开始的时间开始。
So let's just begin in in August and you can do this along with me.
所以让我们从八月份开始，你可以和我一起做。
And there's not only one right answer but we're going to try to make it fit together we're gonna make
不仅有一个正确的答案，而且我们要努力使它适合我们要做的
it make sense in August.
八月是有道理的。
I'm I'm going I'm going on.
我去 我去
OK so we could just say going on a trip but I'd like to make it a little more interesting.
好的，所以我们可以说去旅行，但我想让它更有趣一点。
So I'm going to I'm going to change it up a little bit.
所以我要去我要稍微改变一下。
Going on a solo add an additive there solo trip solo means by yourself.
独自旅行添加一个添加剂在那里独自旅行独自意味着自己。
OK.
好的。
So a little trip to to Australia.
所以来了一次澳大利亚之旅。
Simple enough first sentence.
很简单的第一句话。
Very simple but we fit it together.
非常简单，但我们将它组合在一起。
We could do it in a different way though.
不过，我们可以用不同的方式来做。
OK.
好的。
We could say next August we could start.
我们可以说明年八月我们就可以开始了。
We probably couldn't put it in the past tense because of what's going to be there later.
我们可能不能把它放在过去时，因为稍后会发生什么。
But we could change it around a lot.
但我们可以改变很多。
And you can play with it to get a feeling for how to link these these different words together.
你可以用它来感受一下如何将这些不同的词联系在一起。
OK.
好的。
Then we start let's see next week buy tickets.
那我们就开始看下周买票吧。
That's an easy one.
这很容易。
Next week I need to make my I'm going to add make my itinerary make my itinerary temporary is your travel
下周我需要让我的我要添加 让我的行程 让我的行程临时是你的旅行
travel plan.
旅行计划。
Make my itinerary and we're gonna have buy tickets there too.
制定我的行程，我们会买票也有。
So we can add a lot of things if we want between words and bye by my.
所以如果我们想在单词和 by my.bye 之间添加很多东西。
Well if we just say tickets then it could be train tickets so I want to make sure it's clear.
好吧，如果我们只是说车票，那可能是火车票，所以我想确保清楚。
So my plane tickets.
所以我的机票。
Now we have here my very close to my.
现在我们在这里非常接近我的。
Is it is it OK that we do that.
我们这样做可以吗。
Yeah.
是的。
So it's OK that we do that.
所以我们可以这样做。
We could also probably make our own sentence here if we wanted to with the last part we could say I
如果我们愿意，我们也可以在这里自己造句，最后一部分我们可以说我
will also buy my plane tickets.
也会买我的机票。
That would be another small sentence.
那将是另一个小句子。
That's OK.
没关系。
To both of these are ok ok.
对这两个都可以。
So let's keep going with this.
所以让我们继续这个。
I.
我。
I plan to to visit Sydney first and then head to Melbourne so we could say that at many many different
我计划先去悉尼，然后再去墨尔本，所以我们可以说在很多不同的地方
ways.
方法。
Go to Melbourne and travel to Melbourne.
前往墨尔本，前往墨尔本。
I plan to visit Sydney and then Melbourne in many many different ways we could say this one as well.
我计划以许多不同的方式访问悉尼，然后是墨尔本，我们也可以这样说。
All right.
好的。
Let's keep going.
我们继续吧。
Again I hope you're doing this as we go along with me.
再次，我希望你在我们和我一起做的时候这样做。
And if you're doing it differently from me that is fine.
如果你的做法与我不同，那很好。
That is fine.
那也行。
All right.
好的。
Let's see what's next.
让我们看看接下来会发生什么。
As soon as that means exactly when as soon as I arrive at my hotel and check in.
只要这意味着我到达酒店并登记入住的确切时间。
All I want to do is find a place to relax by the ocean.
我想做的就是在海边找个地方放松一下。
OK.
好的。
Very simple.
很简单。
But what made this all one sentence and we've added some interesting stuff between the words we have
但是是什么让这一切成为一个句子，我们在我们拥有的单词之间添加了一些有趣的东西
to use.
使用。
We have to use hotel right.
我们必须使用酒店权利。
We have to use arrive.
我们必须使用到达。
We have to use relax.
我们必须使用放松。
We have to use ocean.
我们必须使用海洋。
But Queen that we can do really what we want.
但是女王说我们真的可以做我们想做的事。
We can add more we can add less.
我们可以添加更多，我们可以添加更少。
Again you could make it a much longer story.
同样，您可以使它成为一个更长的故事。
If you want to let's keep going.
如果你想继续，我们继续。
I'm gonna add something that's not here at all.
我要添加一些根本不在这里的东西。
That's what that's that's what they occasions are all about.
这就是他们的场合的全部内容。
That's what vacations are all about.
这就是假期的全部意义所在。
Woo hoo.
呜呼。
Add an exclamation there.
在那里添加一个感叹号。
It's called an exclamation.
它被称为感叹号。
I really hope.
我真的希望。
And really why not.
真的为什么不呢。
We have to use hope.
我们必须使用希望。
And really I really hope I can meet a lot of Oh that's so weird.
真的，我真的希望我能遇到很多哦，这太奇怪了。
Oh a lot of interesting people while I'm there.
哦，当我在那里时，有很多有趣的人。
Again we could say in Australia we could say there we could say while I'm on my trip we could say all
再说一次，我们可以在澳大利亚说我们可以说在那里我们可以说当我在旅途中我们可以说所有
of these things but the most important is that we are working within our rules.
其中最重要的是我们正在按照我们的规则工作。
We have our clear rules right.
我们有正确的明确规则。
We've got do we have interesting people.
我们有没有有趣的人。
Yes interesting people is here.
是的，有趣的人在这里。
Do we have hope.
我们有希望吗。
First yes hope is right there.
首先是的希望就在那里。
And because those are the only two we're going to include here we have a lot more freedom can express
因为这两个是我们要在这里包含的仅有的两个，所以我们有更多的自由可以表达
something very interesting.
非常有趣的事情。
Now the last part the last part.
现在是最后一部分，最后一部分。
Here we go.
开始了。
Last part at here we kind of have to say at it could say around the beginning of September but you probably
在这里的最后一部分，我们不得不说它可能会在 9 月初左右说，但你可能
at at the beginning could say in the beginning as well at the beginning of September.
在开始时可以说在开始时以及在九月初。
Hope you don't mind if I just write S E P T at the beginning of September.
希望你不介意我在九月初写 S E P T。 我需要飞回家并重返工作岗位。
We could also say get back to work.
我们也可以说回去工作。
I need to fly back home and get back to work.
我需要飞回家，回去工作。
If we say back to times in a row it can sound a little bit weird.
如果我们连续说回时间，这听起来有点奇怪。
So I think return to work would be better if we took out back then maybe it would be OK and we could
所以我认为如果我们回去工作会更好，也许会没事，我们可以
say I need to fly home and get back to work.
说我需要飞回家并回去工作。
That would be just fine.
那样就好了。
So you've got to play around with this if you want to do it on your own.
所以如果你想自己做，你必须玩这个。
All you do is find a text an article whatever.
你所要做的就是找到一篇文章一篇文章。
Pick out some of the keywords from there.
从那里挑选一些关键字。
Write them down on a piece of paper in the correct order.
以正确的顺序将它们写在一张纸上。
You can write it just like this with the single word followed by a period just to make it simple.
为了简单起见，您可以像这样用一个单词后跟一个句点来编写它。
Then at the bottom underneath that write your own little story and fill in the spaces and you want to
然后在下面的底部写下你自己的小故事并填写你想要的空间
try to make sure that it all makes sense.
尝试确保这一切都有意义。
You want to have different types of sentences different lengths different types of grammar that you're
你想有不同类型的句子不同长度不同类型的语法，你是
using in the sentences and very importantly you want to make it interesting.
在句子中使用，非常重要的是你想让它变得有趣。
It's got to be interesting.
一定很有趣。
OK let's go on and look at the next exercise that we can do which is similar to this but we're going
好的，让我们继续看看我们可以做的下一个练习，它与此类似，但我们将继续
to be actually simplifying and removing some things that are unnecessary.
实际上是简化和删除一些不必要的东西。